# MR ASHOK BHADRAPPA

24/06/1985 Date of birth:

Nationality: India

1123 Sarathy Nagar 1st Block J P Nagar 8th

Address: Phase, Bengaluru 560076, India

Phone number: 9731808033

Email address: ashokbhadrappa@gmail.com



# PROFILE

#### What I have to offer

I have 12.5 years of experience in IT services, where in I have held responsible positions specialising in IT services as a programmer, module lead, technical lead, solution designer. My practical experience includes solution designing & architecture, support, software development, testing, specifications, security policy and people management.

#### What I'm looking for. Is this you?

- Company with a positive ethical stance
- Direct engineering hands-on involvement
- Manage a small team
- Time and opportunity to learn and apply emerging technologies

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Senior Technology Architect

05/2020 - present Infosys, Bangalore, India

**Solution Architect** 08/2010 - 05/2020 Wipro Limited, Bengaluru, India

- Leading a transformation of current On-Premise services to cloud including the infrastructure and networking design
- Leading an In-House development team using agile methodology, providing coaching to new members of the team and setting the development standards
- Responsible for architecting, designing and implementing complete solution delivery covering BPM, restful APIs, AWS for a major Bank in UK in its digital transformation
- Accountable in solution Design, Development and Delivery of Package Implementations, Process Integration, System Analysis, Data Analysis, Data Mapping.
- Experience in all the areas of software life cycle, lead the project teams to successfully deliver solutions with the highest quality in challenging customer environments.
- Working with Business users, Production gather the requirements, to understanding the business intent and solutioning the business intent with the scalable solution

# WORK EXPERIENCE

01/2008 - 08/2010 Software Engineer CSC India Pvt Ltd, Bengaluru, India

- Accountable in Requirement Analysis.
- Providing support during integration of submodules.
- Understanding the end-end business requirements.
- Involved in the development using technologies such as Java/J2EE, JCAPS.
- Peer Review of LLD, UTC, JCAPS Projects.
- Fixing and testing high priority defects.

## EDUCATION

09/2003 - 07/2007 Malnad College of Engineering, Hassan, India

# 🚣 SKILLS

#### **Technical Skills**

Design & Architecture Java AWS, Spring, SpringBoot JAX-WS,JAX-RS Oracle BPM & SOA Docker, Kubernetes Apache Kafka, JMS Microservices



#### Application & Web Servers

Weblogic & Tomcat

#### Tools

SVN, Github, Jenkins Clearcase



# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Oracle Unified Business Process Management Suite 11g Certified Implementation Specialist

### 🤒 SOCIAL MEDIA





